(Howard:)Not until he stops humping
his way up my family tree!
(Amy:)Sheldon, this is silly.
(Amy:)I'm not missing another prom.
(Amy:)I'm going upstairs now.
(Amy:)Good-bye.
(Sheldon:)I really did think
you looked pretty.
(Amy:)You did?
(Raj:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)So much so that
I started to panic.
(Amy:)Well, you can relax.
(Amy:)Just because you think
I look pretty
(Amy:)doesn't mean we have
to spend the night together.
(Sheldon:)Were you hoping we would
because it's prom?
(Amy:)I'm always hoping.
(Amy:)But tonight I just wanted
to have a nice time with you.
(Amy:)And maybe dance
with someone who has arms.
(Sheldon:)Thank you for understanding.
(Amy:)Of course I understand.
(Amy:)Sheldon,
(Amy:)there's something else
I've been wanting to say,
(Amy:)but before I do,
I just...
(Amy:)I want you to know that you
don't have to say it back.